Sometimes,
when I wake up in the morning,
I’m crying, but I don’t know why.
Character Design:
Masayoshi Tanaka
(anohana, The Anthem of the Heart)
Animation Director:
Masashi Ando
(Spirited Away, When Marnie Was There)
I can’t ever seem to remember
what I was just dreaming about.
But I know I was searching for something...
or for someone.
I think I’ve been feeling like this since that day.
Director / Script:
Makoto Shinkai
(5 Centimeters Per Second,
The Garden of Words)
That day, when I saw the shooting stars,
Their promises can never meet.
it was like...
Who are you?
Like... something out of a dream.
Mi
tsu
ha
It was such a beautiful sight.
I am searching for you,
whom I have never met yet.