You really aren't normal, are you?
I desire the power to slay Corpses.
You call that fighting?
No wonder so many people have died.
Did you not tell Father
not to point his gun at the wrong person?
She's not a Corpse,
but she's not exactly human either.
That's not a Corpse!
It's my friend!
Are Demicorpses our enemies?
Or are they our allies?
AQWERTYUIOPSDFGHJKLZXCVBNMQWERTYUIOSDFHTRETHH
testaaaaaaa
Araki Tetsurou
An eastern island nation with advanced steam engines
Hinomoto
Twenty years ago,
the people of Hinomoto sought refuge from the Corpses behind the walls of stations.
Undead monsters that appeared without warning
Corpses
Casting aside both friends and dignity alike,
A steam-engine smith
who lives in Aragane Station
they fled for their lives.
Ikoma
Did we lose yet another station?
A girl who was on the Iron Fortress
Mumei
Do you wish to be a hero?
The daughter of Lord Yohogawa
Ayame
What are we but samurai!?
When ought we offer our lives, if not today!?
A young soldier serving the Yohogawa family
Kurusu
Are you stupid, Ikoma?
A steam-engine smith and friend of Ikoma
Takumi
If we can mass-produce the Piercing Pipe Cannon, we'll be able to fight the Corpses!
You're coming aboard the Iron Fortress with me,
and you're going to be my shield.
Your shield?
It's time to cleanse this filth with extreme prejudice!
Director
Araki Tetsurou
Animation
Series Composition & Script
Okouchi Ichirou
Character Design
Mikimoto Haruhiko
Music
Sawano Hiroyuki
Neither humans nor Corpses,
Demicorpses lie somewhere between.
An enigma lying somewhere
between human and Corpse
Demicorpse
I'm done running away.
Maybe my only chance of surviving is to flee,
but I won't let the lives of others be sacrificed for nothing!
Corpses are the enemy.
I live for one purpose...
to kill every last one of them!